[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city is the apartment from the 1960 comedy movie The Apartment located?", "correct_answer": "New York City", "incorrect_answers": ["Rome", "London", "Paris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the ears of a chinchilla turn red, it is a sign of this condition.", "correct_answer": "Overheating", "incorrect_answers": ["It is pregnant.", "The animal is in heat.", "The animal is disturbed or angry."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to a person who stuffs and mounts animals for display or study?", "correct_answer": "Taxidermist", "incorrect_answers": ["Hunter", "None of these", "Poacher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Half-sizes are for short-waisted women.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Godzilla was originally a cross between a gorilla and a whale.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Talladega Nights, what does Ricky think after he crashes?", "correct_answer": "that he is on fire", "incorrect_answers": ["that he is dreaming", "that he is being chased by a gorilla", "that he is dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Patriot, how many kids does Benjamin have?", "correct_answer": "Seven", "incorrect_answers": ["Six", "Three", "Eight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The world-class hospital in Maryland was named after a person whose last name was Hopkins. What was his first name?", "correct_answer": "Johns", "incorrect_answers": ["Reed", "John", "James"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is an asteroid named Bambi.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Rose Valley is located near the town of Kazanlak, in what major world producer of rose oil?", "correct_answer": "Bulgaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "France", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High is based on a book with the same title, written by which author?", "correct_answer": "Cameron Crowe", "incorrect_answers": ["John Hughes", "Arthur C. Clarke", "Dean Cameron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which kind of breakfast is sometimes referred to as a Full Monty?", "correct_answer": "Full English breakfast", "incorrect_answers": ["Continental breakfast", "Irish breakfast", "French breakfast"]}]